Guide to the Steven H. Scheuer Collection of Television Program Scripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- ALPHABETICAL LISTING OF SCRIPTS BY PROGRAM TITLES
  - GENERAL ELECTRIC THEATER
    - The Lady of the House Jameson Brewer, 1956 Jul 25 (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - Town with a Past Oscar Brodney and Frank Burt, 1956 Aug 24 (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - A Child is Born Stephen Vincent Benet, 1956 Dec 23 (Box 121, Folder 18)
    - The Shadow Outside Paul Monash, 1956 Dec 30 (Box 121, Folder 19)
    - A Question of Survival (no author indicated), 1957 May 12 (Box 121, Folder 20)
    - The Charlatan Wells Root, 1957 Jun 23 (Box 121, Folder 21)
    - The Influential Americans (special) with Howard K. Smith, 1960 Nov 13 (Box 121, Folder 22)
    - Prosper's Old Mother William Bowers, undated (Box 121, Folder 23)
    - Lash of Fear James Warner Bellah, undated (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - The Invitation Francis and Marion Cockrell, undated (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Mr. Blue Ocean (title page only) Arthur Steuer, 1955 May 1 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - GENERAL MOTORS PRESENTS
    (Oversize) TV Drama
    Producers: Ron Weyman, Leo Ornstein, Paul Almond
    - Breakthrough (no author indicated), 1958 Oct 5 (Box 451, Folder 2)
    - End of Summer Elliott Baker, 1958 Oct 12 (Box 451, Folder 3)
    - Men Don't Make Passes Bernard Slade, 1958 Nov 2 (Box 451, Folder 4)
    - The Flower in the Rock Joseph Schell, undated (Box 451, Folder 5)
  - THE GEORGE GOBEL SHOW
    Producers: Hal Kanter, Al Lewis, Jack Donohue, Alan Handley, Bill Burch, Harry Tugend
    Directors: Bud Yorkin, Dick McDonough, Jack Donohue, Alan Handley, Norman Abbott
    Writers: Norman Lear, Leo Solomon, Tom Koch, Don Beaumont, Paul Scully, Artie Philips
    - Episode #4, 1954 Oct 30 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Episode #10, 1954 Dec 25 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Episode #13, 1955 Jan 22 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Episode #14, 1955 Jan 29 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Episode #15, 1955 Feb 5 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Episode #1, 1955 Oct 8 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Episode #2, 1955 Oct 15 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Episode #3, 1955 Oct 22 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Episode #4, 1955 Oct 29 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Episode #6, 1955 Nov 19 (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Episode #9, 1955 Dec 17 (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Episode #11, 1956 Jan 7 (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Episode #14, 1956 Feb 4 (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Episode #17, 1956 Mar 3 (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - Episode #19, 1956 Mar 24 (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - Episode #20, 1956 Mar 31 (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - Episode #21, 1956 Apr 7 (Box 122, Folder 19)
    - Episode #22, 1956 Apr 21 (Box 122, Folder 20)
    - Episode #23, 1956 Apr 28 (Box 122, Folder 21)
    - Episode #25, 1956 May 19 (Box 122, Folder 22)
    - Episode #26, 1956 May 26 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Episode #27, 1956 Jun 2 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Episode #29, 1956 Jun 23 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Episode #30, 1956 Jun 30 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Episode #1, 1956 Oct 6 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Episode #2, 1956 Oct 13 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Episode #3, 1956 Oct 20 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Episode #4, 1956 Nov 3 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Episode #7, 1956 Dec 1 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Episode #9 (incomplete), 1956 Dec 15 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Episode #12, 1957 Jan 12 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Episode #13, 1957 Jan 26 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Episode #16, 1957 Feb 9 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Episode #17, 1957 Mar 2 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Episode #18, 1957 Mar 9 (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Episode #19, 1957 Mar 23 (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Episode #20, 1957 Mar 30 (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Episode #21, 1957 Apr 6 (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Episode #22, 1957 Apr 20 (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - Episode #23, 1957 Apr 27 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Episode #24, 1957 May 4 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Episode #25, 1957 May 18 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Episode #26, 1957 May 25 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Episode #27, 1957 Jun 1 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Episode #28, 1957 Jun 15 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Episode #2, 1957 Oct 8 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Episode #3, 1957 Oct 22 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Episode #4, 1957 Nov 5 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Episode #5, 1957 Nov 19 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Episode #6, 1957 Dec 3 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Episode #7, 1957 Dec 17 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Episode #8, 1957 Dec 31 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - 1958 Jan 28 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Episode #10, 1958 Feb 11 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Episode #11, 1958 Feb 25 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Episode #12, 1958 Mar 11 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Episode #13, 1958 Mar 25 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Episode #16, 1958 May 6 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Episode #17, 1958 May 20 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Episode #1, 1958 Sep 23 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Episode #2, 1958 Oct 7 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Episode #3, 1958 Oct 21 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Episode #4, 1958 Nov 4 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Episode #5, 1958 Nov 18 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Episode #6, 1958 Dec 2 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - 1958 Dec 16 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - 1958 Dec 30 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Episode #9, 1959 Jan 13 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Episode #10, 1959 Jan 27 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Episode #11, 1959 Feb 24 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - 2 fragments (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - THE GEORGE JESSEL SHOW
    Producer: Mannie Manheim
    Director: Edward Nugent
    Writers: George Jessel and Sam Carlton
    - 1953 Nov 15 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - 1953 Nov 22 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - 1953 Nov 29 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - 1953 Dec 6 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - 1953 Dec 13 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - 1953 Dec 27 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - 1954 Jan 3 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - 1954 Jan 17 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - 1954 Jan 31 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - 1954 Feb 14 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - 1954 Feb 28 (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - 1954 Mar 7 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - 1954 Mar 14 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - 1954 Mar 21 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - 1954 Mar 28 (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - 1954 Apr 4 (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - GLENN MILLER TIME
    Producer: Bill Harbach
    Director: Bob Scheerer
    Writer: Marty Roth
    - 1961 Jul 10 (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - 1961 Jul 24 (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - THE GOLDBERGS
    Situation comedy
    Producer: Cherney R. Berg
    Director: Martin Magnen
    Writer: Gertrude Berg
    - 1953 Jul 3 (Box 127, Folder 19)
    - 1953 Jul 10 (Box 127, Folder 20)
    - 1953 Jul 17 (Box 127, Folder 21)
    - 1953 Jul 24 (Box 127, Folder 22)
    - 1953 Aug 7 (2 copies) (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - 1953 Aug 14 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - 1953 Aug 21 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - 1953 Aug 28 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - 1953 Sep 4 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - 1953 Sep 18 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - 1953 Sep 25 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - 1954 May 4 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - 1954 May 11 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - 1954 Jun 1 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - 1954 Jun 29 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - 1954 Jul 13 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - 1954 Jul 20 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - 1954 Jul 27 (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - 1954 Aug 10 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - 1954 Sep 14 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - 1954 Sep 21 (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - 1954 Sep 28 (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - 1954 Oct 5 (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - 1954 Oct 12 (Box 128, Folder 20)
  - THE GOODYEAR TELEVISION PLAYHOUSE
    See: also "Alcoa Hour," The Sentry (undated), and The Treasure Hunters (undated)
  - THE GOODYEAR TELEVISION PLAYHOUSE
    TV drama NBC
    Producers: Fred Coe, David Susskind, Gordon Duff, Herbert Brodkin, Philip Barry, Robert Mulligan, Jack Smight, Herbert Hirschman, Paul Bogart, Alex Segal
    Directors: Vincent J. Donohue, Delbert Mann, William Corrigan, Arthur Penn, Jeffrey Hayden
    - The Gesture Ira Avery, 1953 Mar 15 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Wish on the Moon Sumner Locke Elliott, 1953 Mar 29 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Printer's Measure Paddy Chayefsky, 1953 Apr 26 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Expectant Relations Horton Foote, 1953 Jun 21 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Catch a Falling Star Thomas W. Phipps, 1953 Jun 28 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Incident in Athens N. Richard Nash, 1953 Jul 5 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - The Big Deal Paddy Chayefsky, 1953 Jul 19 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - The Cipher Irving Gaynor Neiman, 1953 Aug 2 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Other People's Houses Tad Mosel, 1953 Aug 30 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - The Bachelor Party Paddy Chayefsky, 1953 Oct 11 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - The Girl with the Stopwatch Sumner Locke Elliott, 1953 Oct 25 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - The Train to Trouble Harry Muheim, 1953 Nov 8 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Up Above the World So High Greer Johnson, 1953 Nov 22 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Madame Aphrodite Tad Mosel, 1953 Dec 6 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Moment of Panic Sumner Locke Elliott, 1954 Jan 3 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Spring Reunion Robert Alan Aurthur, 1954 Apr 11 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Old Tasselfoot (2 copies) J. P. Miller, 1954 Apr 25 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Miss Look-alike Mann Rubin, 1954 May 9 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Somebody Special J. P. Miller, 1954 Jun 6 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Suitable for Framing Harry Muheim, 1954 Jul 4 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - The Arena N. Richard Nash, 1954 Aug 1 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Recoil A. J. Russel, 1954 Aug 15 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - The Power of Suggestion David Shaw, 1954 Aug 29 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Big Man on the Campus Robert Alan Aurthur, 1954 Sep 12 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Guilty is the Stranger Tad Mosel, 1954 Sep 26 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Last Boat from Messina David Shaw, 1954 Dec 5 (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Class of '58 Louis S. Peterson, 1954 Dec 19 (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - Doing Her Bit Roger Hirson, 1955 Jan 16 (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - My Lost Saints Tad Mosel, 1955 Mar 13 (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Beloved Stranger (incomplete) Sumner Locke Elliott, 1955 Apr 10 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Do-It-Yourself Jay Presson, 1955 Apr 24 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - The Catered Affair Paddy Chayefsky, 1955 May 22 (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Mr. Dorothy Allan Roger Hirson, 1955 Jun 5 (Box 132, Folder 8)
    - End of the Mission Roger Hirson, 1955 Jun 19 (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Man on Spikes Eliot Asinof, 1955 Jul 17 (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Tangled Web Audrey and William Roos, 1955 Jul 3 (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - The Takers William Manchester, 1955 Aug 14 (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - Suit Yourself Jim Fritzell, 1955 Sep 11 (Box 133, Folder 5)
    - Merry Go Round Mann Rubin, 1955 Sep 25 (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - A Business Proposition John Vlahos, 1955 Oct 23 (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - One Mummy Too Many Alvin Sapinsley, 1955 Nov 20 (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Starlet John Vlahos, 1956 Jan 29 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - Kyria Katina John Vlahos, 1956 Feb 12 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - The Terrorists Jerome Coopersmith, 1956 Feb 26 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Joey Louis Peterson, 1956 Mar 25 (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Career Girl Jerome Ross, 1956 Apr 22 (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - The Primary Colors Jack Paritz, 1956 Jun 3 (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Sound the Pipes of Pan John Vlahos, 1956 Jun 17 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - The Filmaker Malvin Wald Jack Jacob, 1956 Jul 1 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Pencil Sketch Abby Mann, 1956 Jul 29 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Proud Passage Joseph Schull, 1956 Aug 12 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - Grow Up! Peggy Lamson, 1956 Aug 26 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - Ark of Safety (2 copies) Frances Goforth and Howard Richardson, 1956 Sep 9 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - Maestro John Vlahos, 1956 Sep 23 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - Nobody's Town Harold Swanton, 1957 Jan 27 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - The Princess Back Home John Van Druten, 1957 Feb 24 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - First Love Hedda Rosten, 1957 Mar 24 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - The Gene Austin Story Ernest Kinoy, 1957 Apr 21 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Your Every Wish Clifford Goldsmith, 1957 Jun 16 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - The Legacy Steven Gethers, 1957 Jun 30 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Rumbin Galleries Therese Lewis, 1957 Jul 28 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Weekend in Vermont Ernest Kinoy, 1957 Aug 4 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - The Dark Side of the Moon Arthur Sainer, 1957 Aug 18 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - The Littlest Leaguer Blanche Hanalis, 1957 Aug 25 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - The House Art Wallace, 1957 Sep 8 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - The Last of the Wine John Vlahos, 1957 Sep 29 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - A Murder is Announced William Templeton, undated (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - GREAT GHOST TALES (Box 138)
    Suspense drama
    Producers: Audrey Gellen
    Directors: Daniel Petrie, Lewis Freedman, Allen Reisner, Karl Genus Seymour, Robbie Ron Winston, Lewis Freedman
    Writers: Robert Thom, Joel Carpenter, Audrey Gellen, Elliott Baker, W. F. Harvey, Phil Reisman, Gordon Russell
    - Episode #1, 1961 Jul 6 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Episode #2, 1961 Jul 13 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Episode #3, 1961 Jul 20 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Episode #4, 1961 Jul 27 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Episode #5 (2 copies), 1961 Aug 3 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Episode #10, undated (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Episode #11, 1961 Sep 14 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - undated (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - GULF PLAYHOUSE
    TV Drama NBC
    Directors: Bob Costell, Arthur Penn
    (Few dates indicated--ca. summer 1953--so scripts are filed according to program number.)
    - Episode #2 I'd Rather Be a Squirrel Harry Muheim (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Episode #3 The Death of the Old Man Horton Foote (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Episode #5 One Night Stand Robert Alan Aurthur (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Episode #6 August Heat Nelson Olmsted (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Episode #7 The Tears of My Sister Horton Foote, 1953 Aug 14 (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Episode #9 The Lady Looks Ahead Harry Muheim (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Episode #10 Prophet in His Land Doug Johnson, 1953 Sep 4 (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - Episode #13 A Gift from Cotton Mather Paddy Chayefsky (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - GUNSMOKE
    Western series
    Producer: Charles Marquis Warren
    Writers: John Dunkel, Harold Swanton, John Meston, Gil Doud, Sam Peckinpah, Winston Miller, David Victor, Charles Marquis Warren, Herbert Little, Jr., Tom Hanley, William Leicester, Les Crutchfield
    (No dates or numbers indicated; scripts are filed alphabetically according to titles.)
    - Alarm at Pleasant Valley (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Big Broad (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Bloody Hands (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Cara (2 copies) (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Chester's Mail-Order Bride (2 copies) (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Cooter (2 copies) (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Cow Doctor (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Custer (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Doc's Revenge (2 copies) (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Dutch George (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - General Parsley Smith (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - Greater Love (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - The Guitar (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Home Surgery (Box 139, Folder 14)
    - Homecoming (Kansas Landing) (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Hot Spell (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - How to Cure a Friend (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - How to Die for Nothing (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - The Hunter (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Indian Scout (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Indian White (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Legal Killing (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Magnus (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - The Mistake (2 copies) (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Mr. & Mrs. Amber (2 copies) (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - No Indians (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - The Pest Hole (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - The Photographer (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Poor Pearl (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Prairie Happy (2 copies) (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - The Preacher (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Professor Lute Bone (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Puckett's New Year (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - The Reed Survives (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Reunion '78 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Reward For Matt (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Smoking Out the Nolans (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Spring Term (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Unmarked Grave (2 copies) (Box 141, Folder 12)
    - Word of Honor (Box 141, Folder 13)
    - Yorky (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - Young Man with a Gun (2 copies) (Box 141, Folder 15)
  - HALLMARK HALL OF FAME
    1953-54: historical and biographical dramas
    1958-63 plays adapted for TV
    Directors: Albert McCleery, Norman Felton, and George Schaefer
    - Horace Mann's Miracle Rod Serling, 1953 Mar 8 (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - The Harp of Erin Ellen and Richard McCracken, 1953 Mar 15 (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Photographed by Brady Robert Mason Pollock, 1953 Mar 22 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - A Queen is Born Robert Mason Pollock, 1953 Mar 29 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - The Other Wise Man Harold Gallen, 1953 Apr 5 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Skipper of the Skies Robert Mason Pollock, 1953 Apr 12 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - The World on a Wire Ellen and Richard McCracken, 1953 Apr 19 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - No Man is an Island Helene Hanff, 1953 May 3 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - The Lady of Liberty Harold Gallen, 1953 May 10 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Soldier of Peace Robert Mason Pollock, 1953 May 17 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Proudly I Love John Schwartz, 1953 May 24 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Spark of Genius Elaine Ryan, 1953 May 31 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - The Clay of Kings Elaine Ryan, 1953 Jun 7 (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Scott's Castle Elizabeth Hart, 1953 Jun 14 (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - Man Against Pain Rod Serling, 1953 Jun 21 (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - The Mercer Girls Poot Pray, 1953 Jun 28 (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - Of Time and the River Howard Rodman, 1953 Oct 4 (Box 142, Folder 17)
    - A Queen's Way Jennette and Francis Letton, 1953 Oct 11 (Box 142, Folder 18)
    - Never Kick a Man Upstairs James Truex, 1953 Oct 25 (Box 142, Folder 19)
    - The Imaginary Invalid Maurice Valency, 1953 Nov 1 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - The Lonely Way Eileen and Robert Mason Pollock, 1953 Nov 8 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - The Courtship of Miles Standish Ellen and Richard McCracken, 1953 Nov 22 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Aesop and Rhodope Helene Hanff, 1953 Dec 13 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Blaze of Darkness Eileen and Robert Mason Pollock, 1953 Dec 27 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - John Marshall and the Burr Case Ellen and Richard McCracken, 1954 Jan 3 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Crusade to Liberty Eileen and Robert Mason Pollock, 1954 Jan 10 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - The Hands of Clara Schumann Helene Hanff, 1954 Feb 7 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Crusader against Cruelty Harold Callen, 1954 Feb 14 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Miss Tracy of Mr. Vernon Elaine Ryan, 1954 Feb 21 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - The Good Samaritan Harold Callen, 1954 Mar 7 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - The Ordeal of Thomas Jefferson Helene Hanff, 1954 Mar 28 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Moby Dick Howard Rodman, 1954 Apr 4 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Young William Penn James Truex, 1954 Apr 4 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - The Liberator Howard Rodman, 1954 Apr 11 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - The Story of Ruth Howard Rodman, 1954 Apr 18 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Lafayette for Freedom Ellen and Richard McCracken, 1954 Apr 25 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Petticoat Revolution Helene Hanff, 1954 May 2 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Portrait by Whistler Ted Wear, 1954 May 9 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - The Armour-Bearer Helene Hanff, 1954 May 30 (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Dynamite Harold Callen, 1954 Sep 5 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Do Not Cry For Me Eileen and Robert Mason Pollock, 1954 Sep 12 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - A Man of Many Ideas (2 copies) Boris Sagal, 1954 Sep 19 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - The Reluctant Redeemer Helene Hanff, 1954 Sep 26 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - The Lady in the Wings Helene Hanff, 1954 Oct 24 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - The Path to Peace Eileen and Robert Mason Pollock, 1954 Oct 31 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - President for a Day Nelson Gidding, 1954 Nov 21 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Deadlock Eugene Vale, 1954 Dec 5 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - The Joyful Tydings Elaine Ryan, 1954 Dec 26 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Hans Brinker or The Silver Skates, 1958 Feb 9 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Green Pastures Marc Connelly, 1959 Mar 23 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - The Teahouse of the August Moon Robert Hartung, 1962 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Pygmalion Robert Hartung (G. B. Shaw), 1963 Feb 6 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Ah, Wilderness Robert Hartung (Eugene O'Neill), undated (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Berkeley Square Theodore Apstein, undated (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - The St. Cloud Storm Ellen and Richard McCracken, undated (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - A Smile for Danger Harold Callen, undated (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - McCoy of Abilene Harold Callen, undated (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - The Borrowed Christmas (no author indicated), undated (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - HOLLYWOOD SCREEN TEST
    Writer: Alton Alexander
    - A Model Young Woman, 1953 Mar 2 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - The Pen is Mightier Than Parole, 1953 Mar 16 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - "Foster" Joe, 1953 Mar 30 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Bequest Delayed, 1953 Apr 20 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - For the Love of Mike, undated (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - The Poe Letter, undated (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - (no title), undated (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - HONESTLY, CELESTE!
    Situation comedy, with Celeste Holm
    Producers-Directors: Joseph Scibetta, David Alexander
    Writers: Larry Gelbart, Hal Collins, Jack Raymond, Mike Miller
    - 1954 Oct 10 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - 1954 Oct 31 (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - 1954 Nov 7 (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - 1954 Nov 21 (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - 1954 Nov 28 (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - 1954 Nov 28 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - 1954 Dec 5 (Box 147, Folder 17)
  - THE HONEYMOONERS
    Situation comedy, with Jackie Gleason and Audrey Meadows
    (no dates indicated)
    - Boys and Girls Together (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - A Letter to the Boss (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Principle of the Thing (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - The Hypnotist (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - THE INVESTIGATOR
    Producer: William M. Altman
    Directors: William A. Graham, Robert Ellis Miller, Eliot Silverstein
    Writers: Henry Kane, Charles Quaid, Louis Pelletier, Nicholas Baehr
    Harold Gast, Irving Elman
    - Episode #1, 1958 Jun 3 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Episode #2, 1958 Jun 10 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Episode #4, 1958 Jun 24 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Episode #6, 1958 Jul 8 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Episode #7, 1958 Jul 22 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Episode #8, 1958 Jul 29 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Episode #9, 1958 Aug 5 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Episode #12, 1958 Sep 2 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - THE JACK BENNY SHOW
    - 1954 Nov 14 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - 1954 Nov 28 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - 1954 Dec 27 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - 1955 Jan 1 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - 1955 Jan 23 (2 copies) (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - 1955 Jan 23 (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - 1955 Feb 20 (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - 1955 Mar 20 (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - 1955 Apr 3 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - 1955 Apr 17 (2 copies) (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - 1955 May (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - 1955 Oct 23 (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - 1955 Dec 4 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - 1955 Dec 18 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - 1956 Jan 29 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - 1956 Feb 12 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - 1956 Mar 25 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - 1956 Apr 8 (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - 1956 Apr 25 (2 copies) (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - 1956 Jun 3 (BBC Special) (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - undated (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - undated (Box 150, Folder 16)
  - THE JACKIE GLEASON SHOW
    Producers: Jack Hurdle, Jack Philbin
    Directors: Frank Satinstein, Seymour Robbie, Framl Bimetta
    Writers: Harry Crane, Howard Harris, Marvin Marx, Hank Ladd, Walter Stone, Walter Kempley, Al Schwartz, Hugh Wedlock, Sidney Zelinka, Snag Werris, Will Glickman, Sidney Reznick, James Shelton, Roger Price, Mel Diamond
    - Episode #34, 1953 May 16 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - 1957 Feb 16 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - 1957 Apr 20 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - 1957 Apr 27 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - 1957 May 11 (Box 151, Folder 5)